[
    {
        "Id": 1,
        "question": "We don't visit you very often because you live so far away.",
        "answer": "If you didn't live so far away, we would visit you more often."


    },
    {
        "Id": 2,
        "question": "He doesn't speak very clearly - that's why people don't understand him.",
        "answer": "If he spoke more clearly, people would undestand him."

    },
    {
        "Id": 3,
        "question": "That book is too expensive, so I'm not going to buy it.",
        "answer": "If that book wasn't so expensive, I'd buy it."

    },
    {
        "Id": 4,
        "question": "We don't go out very often because we can't afford it.",
        "answer": "If we could afford it, we'd go out more often."

    },
    {
        "Id": 5,
        "question": "It's raining, so we can't have lunch in the garden.",
        "answer": "If it wasn't raining, we could have lunch in the garden."

    },
    {
        "Id": 6,
        "question": "I have to work tomorrow evening, so I can't meet you.",
        "answer": "If I didn't have to work tommorow evening, I would meet you."

    },
    {
        "Id": 7,
        "question": "I can't go out because I haven't got any money.",
        "answer": "I would go out if I had some money."

    },
    {
        "Id": 8,
        "question": "Steve doesn't like Harry because he talks too much.",
        "answer": "Steve would like Harry if he didn't talk so much."

    },
    {
        "Id": 9,
        "question": "I get sleepy when I watch a boring film.",
        "answer": "I wouldn't get sleepy if I watched an interesting film."

    },
    {
        "Id": 10,
        "question": "I get sleepy when I watch a boring film.",
        "answer": "I wouldn't get sleepy if I watched an interesting film."

    },
    {
        "Id": 11,
        "question": "It's raining so I'll stay at home.",
        "answer": "I would go out if it stopped lub wasn't raining."

    },
    {
        "Id": 12,
        "question": "I'll be happy when I find a job.",
        "answer": "I would be happy if I found a job."

    },
    {
        "Id": 13,
        "question": "I can't fix my bike unless my brother helps me.",
        "answer": "I could fix my bike if my brother helped me."

    },
    {
        "Id": 14,
        "question": "I'll be late for work if I forget to set my alarm.",
        "answer": "I would be late for work if I forgot to set my alarm."

    },
    {
        "Id": 15,
        "question": "Ask Ernie. He'll know what to do.",
        "answer": "Ernie would tell you what to do if you asked him."

    },
    {
        "Id": 16,
        "question": "There's no pudding today. We haven't got any milk.",
        "answer": "I would make lub could make a pudding if we had some milk."

    },
    {
        "Id": 17,
        "question": "Those eggs are old. I can't make an omelette with them.",
        "answer": "I could make lub would make an omelette if the eggs were not lub weren't old."

    }
]